[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete the title of a song by the rock group Creedence Clearwater Revival: Proud _____", "correct_answer": "Mary", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry", "Berry", "Barry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What movie was Leonardo DiCaprios debut?", "correct_answer": "This Boys Life", "incorrect_answers": ["Dons Plum", "Whats Eating Gilbert Grape", "The Quick and the Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What vegetable is used for the preparation of the traditional Arab dish called Baba ghanoush?", "correct_answer": "Eggplant", "incorrect_answers": ["Potato", "Carrot", "Tomato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Empire Strikes Back, Darth Vader captures Han Solo and Chewbacca on what planet?", "correct_answer": "Bespin", "incorrect_answers": ["Alderaan", "Hoth", "Tatooine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Destry Rides Again was a comedy/western/love story that featured Marlene Dietrich, Mischa Auer, Brian Donleavy, and Billy Gilbert. Who played the title character?", "correct_answer": "James Stewart", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry Fonda", "Humphrey Bogart", "Jack Carson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What California city is the setting for the 1953 Science Fiction classic Phantom from Space?", "correct_answer": "Santa Monica", "incorrect_answers": ["San Diego", "L.A.", "Sacramento"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is true about the eyelids?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["They protect the eye from drying out and from foreign objects.", "The skin of the eyelids contains more pigment cells compared to the rest of the skin on the body.", "The skin of the eyelids is one of the thinnest skin of the whole human body."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor sans intestines, bellows Freedomm in a movie listed under the category of Five Cool Deaths by Weekly Entertainment?", "correct_answer": "Mel Gibson", "incorrect_answers": ["Matt Damon", "Russell Crow", "Samuel Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Star Wars character Obi-Wan kill General Grievous?", "correct_answer": "Utapau", "incorrect_answers": ["Felucia", "Kessel", "Mustafar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The molars of todays African elephant can be longer than a foot.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a synonym for humor based on sexual explicit situations.", "correct_answer": "blue humor", "incorrect_answers": ["vitreous humor", "baud talk", "red humor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Light waves travel in a straight line.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]